I am. And I will be there. I will make him
suffer like I accept. The words of
a sadist one of the most disruptive
elements in human society to have complete
mastery over another to make him
a helpless object to humiliate you to
win sway you to inflict moral in the
sanity on the innocent that is his
objective his twisted glacier.
Early.
A strange looking place.
But I thought your pop
along you think will take it a big
head to be replaced take about
a half an hour they had the party. Should
have won with all these wrecks around
here.
That guy was good for time and have car
trouble you got problems for that to happen
I'm glad it happened more I did and when
it did I didn't much relish the idea of
being stuck in those mountains they were
lucky another few miles we have been and
desert is just what you saw to start I'm
afraid so and we still make the game
at forty miles to go. Twelve
or one game doesn't start
a one thirty we can still make it to have
a card. And if they don't play
in stock one Sunday they can
order one from Lancaster.
People that run this place.
And all.
You see when
a play you want to that's why it's the walls
are as bad the player bad as the ball
when I say that the book and it goes over
the same but it's alright I know but if
no one can make him oh why did you have
to run around the bases because he has to
that's the rule he must touch
every base would you like
a coke you. Somebody
can run off of the whole place and the
owner will never know what it is you're.
In the looks of things not the law he was
taking one of the businesses on the King
of. All work is white
collar work this page.
I've. Had my fill of this preparing tax
this prim and proper should have known me
then Doris page is
a sweet girl as the good math
teacher. Little on the previous side
perhaps the boys might do that
class Call the Midwife back.
To. My National Geographic on the
basis when they can't use him.
And that a woman for you never seen
a baseball game and already she's
changing the rules. You should go to
a ball game with my wife
and I still think that's
a silly move. Ever going to see you need
a Father's Day. Guide
It runs this place. And
one about some service. Oh.
I must be around here some place. Doesn't
seem likely they'd go away and leave
everything wide open around
the back. Pay anybody happy.
Oh. Oh.
Bob had already been stripped
of that shit when I do this.
We got ourselves a fuel pump that's
any good well I work on our car take
a few adjustments but you get us down
like I bought you ratchet it will soon be
outta here. Style many times.
A fine young man. Feel like
a woman that's OK. I'm Mr Allison I do
believe you think you put Again you're
only young once myspace page.
I'm just all over you sounds like an old
man. Of fifty two yesterday I think you'd
had
a fine and for my. A nice
home. A lovely wife to have
two children Carl join you graduate from
West Point in two weeks wife and I are
going back to graduation that
we think you're already.
On the ground see if I can find it on.
I don't want to shock you Miss Page. Right
and I guess my shirt during. Those times
I'm lucky that. I don't know.
Top of the same school for over
a year and I still miss Thank you Mr
Styles. And you can get in Dorset sound
a lot better I know I'm
a child be. An open door. Just
a snake in the shed this time of year I
can't stand snakes most people can't part
of the country is loaded with them.
They couldn't. Do they get to be as
much as nine people on.
The highways certainly wrong lessons I. L
L O.
Anybody here
oh.
Come now.
Doris. Ed. Oh.
Hello.
You're never going to fame have to teach
a promoter Lancaster High It really
cuts loose. Today you're really be in
a glory with this red flag I know and you
told me last night that he hasn't seen
a place with
a less than fanatic she said ever since
he got the tickets or something going on
here that just isn't right setting for for
the kitchen table two plates eaten from
and two plates untouched pie still warm.
Separate chapters about the sign of life
that we get out of your
the better off while you.
Just keep working Mr. Putin to fix your
guy just like you intended don't and you
have no right to take our
government. What if I don't fix it.
You fix you direct Mr. You didn't I think
you are no need for the I gotta fix what
happened then mean my
good girl boy. Buddy.
How do we know you'll keep your word looks
like you're just going to have to take
it and you missed it.
The.
When.
You're. In your wallet.
Let's not bikes but you're welcome to it
but we're only schoolteachers young man
you know that duty we
only scooted you we don't
like school teachers do we do the.
Teachers think there's so much
smarter than everybody else.
You have all the money isn't that
another what else do you want.
To keep working Mr.
The. Teachers used to call Judy.
Make fun of. The whole school crime.
Of them and. They're
a pretty good sized boys and what are
tough to be without that gone through.
You only the real big talk is if
you missed it all right peacock.
And of you want to. Come.
T.Q.
Did. You pick up. You real
big native from your lady.
That actually just how big you really are
put down that gun and I'll show you how
big you are and give me three taken for
me to do what I see I've seen you because
that was. One. Tooth you do every time.
You put it on the vendor. Or you
want the good you would think you.
Understand.
Big mean. I did you get your
big you really was. Started
working.
Now I get from one. Man
that's been blinded by his.
Don't you even have
a nice tits let me care for this
man. Acrobats now you know. You
enjoy hurting other people and then
pay em. Balcony and we'll go and
go mother.
I have.
Given it.
This is.
How easy it is. I know what. She does
and that's what the cover result
was leading. Me to my own
outdoors if you can see that.
What do you think you go on this man needs
help is going to get it if you want this
car fixed.
He's going to be all right Doris.
You're lucky Karo
a little more to the right you
wouldn't be here. If we can
get some water in the shed we can stop the
bleeding. What about letting this man
get the shade. Can you be
so cruel you get back in
a car you win enough and.
Hope by all means enjoy your love making.
The very least you can do is the
something on the little
also. Showing on like.
Your love of anonymous.
You haven't got me to
leave her alone it was
a car fixed. And it was fixed to the disk
in the pump by the House do you work in
a car Mr. And you.
Sure to say move Judy. If I
shut your girlfriend is
did. Don't get no ideas
Judy don't know how to use
a good. One
. I wonder why I changed
his mind and I don't
like this I know something else you won't
like her remember really last week about
the brutal killings in Arizona.
You play me but why are you
putting us through this touch.
You have our money and you're taking our
cars and other now if you keep your duty
and softening you thank you so
much better than me. You could all
think it would be. Cool
million you all right
I apologize I should have the.
Power to make up call me an enemy.
Hi. I'm sorry your sense of things now can
I call you sorry but you still think it
you think I'm good you think George is
dirt you'll always think it so you don't
think no more you can
mean nothing yeah not. A.
Word or two. Maybe the big
dog who govern world.
Maybe was really good good good
thank you so much better than me.
If I did. Could you could could do.
Oh.
Good you can do thank you so much now.
I'm being such but.
I am. And.
What did he do to you Joe.
Yes there do you want that car fixed you
can do it yourself doesn't even the big
man. Or the big men to get
a name is that Charlie did the big men
who killed seven people made them get on
their knees and shot them in the head
paper cause us real killer must be
a real thrill to wipe out
a family of five only three of the heads
which I left Arizona what about the people
here did you kill them through
a law do you think you can
keep getting away with it is
a law is bound to catch up with you sooner
or later the law has ways of handling
murders he's turned in Tacony so many more
what's going to happen do you get even
a little bit you know polar bear is out.
To some big me and to get back to fix that
car you going to be
a big dead man fast. The
second everybody's becoming
the big talk again abbrev.
Nobody wants to talk no more Judy.
Craig.
Oh.
Yeah.
Just little practice.
Much but. I think we. Are
going to do something to know.
You. Get it.
What are you going to do shut up. Little.
That's Fun us. Down on your knees.
On your knees. Scene is how you like to.
Go and talk all you. To that
seems. You're going to be do
talk. Groovy out for you and.
Talking this to the tundra now. You can't
shoot me like this for no reason for nothing
surely blowing my head off can't give
you
a thrill. It's money
you need I have posted twenty three hundred
dollars in the bank to morrow you can
call my wife sure give it to you all of
it your in your girlfriend could have
a lot of fun on twenty three
hundred dollars. Sure is talking
a lot different than it did
or like girl. You have
a father. Would you want
someone doing this to him.
Think of your old father in
my place. Or your. Save your
breath on him missing on the only thing
in the world is Earl manners did
your old ladies address. Young ladies
can't you realize this is why you
love him don't you you know what it
is to be around someone you love
and who hopes you. Have loved
ones to a daughter a little older
than you. And over there is
a. Breeze
I beg of you talk to her voice. Tell
him this is Rock tell him through his.
Word God just doesn't ever
do anything like that oh.
We're going to unscrew. The. Yellow
girl.
Why.
Can't. You tell Mr Bowman. He
still has to do you talk to
a joke do we. Pick somebody
up something when we
want to get the catalpa Don't you want the
car back into the big man was to take
your place. He says one more word
he will. What about it being
made you feel like token.
Even this good good word to
take its place. I guess nobody
wants to take your place
to.
School teach you.
A. Penny.
That you. Just compose
yourself Oh you want. Me You're
going to post I don't have
a job or have you got the job so.
In another couple of minutes
I'll have the public share
a very long to put another car I
said Shut up you're going to need
a car now and I'm the only one that
can fix it. Wouldn't you love.
Judy the game is soda and but you.
Already know. Who will
anybody be able to tell.
His goods ways to hurt Believe me I feel
as badly as you did had nothing can bring
him back we rely we've got
to think of ourselves now.
Do you think I want to stand there watch
him die what could I do work anyone have
done you can reason with that kid he wants
blood doors and nobody's going to talk
him out of it taught you understand
what we're dealing with he's
a psycho Doris. What should I have
taken his place with that are made
to feel better what would you be saying
to Carl if it was me lying over there.
To get him. To. Ask you where
you would like to thank you.
I just ran. I really you know I'm here.
Because of time before we got five
feet. Dire on the roof
and I get on my knees.
I can. Say I'm drinking.
It.
With.
A pay cut to come by and. See orders
maybe your car will call the police
and you know. You can have my turn.
He didn't tell you who passed by they
do patrol the highway. They will have.
To find
a way to make them stop at.
Story. America do happen but you
can't count on them. All right.
Now listen I'm going to try to find out
how many more shots the has left or if he
has reload or cannot probably
find out. Four shots we
know that leaves four he probably shot
people here too there must have been touring
everywhere Carl told us about the setting
the kitchen to fight seat from and to
place on Top Tips much
a surprise and whether he'd ever to Frankie's
why those two were stuck so. We shot
them that lead to shot we certainly didn't
walk your maybe shot someone else. And
if you had to reload.
Go in Doug misses you talk all you
want you thinking so many is going to
see you why should I fix the car if you're
going to tell us any how you fix it is
that let you live
a little lonely like back did I know
you was still in if you want to
check out you die right now you want this
car tips Who are you fooling you can kill
us but you'll be stranded
that's a road any where there's
a road. Somebody will pick
up the of always here.
So how you got here from Arizona the sale
of Vegas. I've already taken so there's
a rule over. More Shot him to no
i just because he's through. Why
haven't you still got his car ready to
get listening
a shoe is going to let
equations. DO IT IS GO YOU war.
How did you get here from a fifty cent. Is
a great bill den of the relative
peace. I was beginning to elected to.
Shoot him to be sure prayed with the with
remember to reach for this guy to the
Lord Lord. Then your shot of the year.
Between the. What about
the two people you're shot here they pray
to you was again Dem is just don't think
you can bully. Yeah I
know you will I can't.
You know I only fight seven shots.
To get one bullet live in Reloaded.
How many bullets do I have left. It will.
Take you didn't you to be.
The wall Politico's come
on maybe the going to. Come in time you.
Will need to get
a good. But you bet your friend. You
had
a chance Mr you should have
taken it. You legally. You
are yellow B.-O. Duty is freedom in
a big. Big talk.
Is.
Again and.
Ham getting ready to do something.
You owe.
Clinks time I told you they were. Just.
Coming up. They're going to let you know
you're here you know you're not going to
care anymore you're. Getting
back. To you right now.
That's OK.
But
a. Lot of. The
. Stuff.
That I. Believe that.
You know most of. What was
will be very diverse.
Site she makes one point to split from.
Well son.
You're
a scorcher sure it is. I
don't recall I'm seeing you around or before
some. Friend of the family. To talk to
Milton town about an hour ago funny being
the talk of years didn't mention anything
about visitors. He just left for I got in.
I think after. Yeah. Working in the cube
I'm troubled by what Only last week
you know Jim Acosta with thirty
bucks to get a sick boy what
a crock that guy was. Coming
off forty five quid.
Where is melt. Back some place.
Or you get more parts out of a car than
a factory put in it yeah
I hear it can. Thank
.
You.
Get it.
I told you to watch sure
you know what I told you.
I told you nobody good. You're going to
have every officer in California looking
for you they don't scare me nobody
scares me. I'm going to give you
a choice big man you die now or
you fix it guy I'll give you
fifteen minutes to fix it why should I
think that you want to kill us when I get
done I'm giving you fifteen minutes of my
pistol if you want I'll blow your head
off right now is to. Twenty.
You got to one with fifty. Start work.
Right you.
Would ever believe something like this.
OK to shoot who has. What to. COOPER And
Judy give it
a good. Fifteen
. Really good.
To Arizona murder suspect
believed to be. Driving.
License number Mary. Thanks very much back
to ride with the driver this Congress
to send you say that was Robert two
miles east of proximately tend to stay.
Right there. Next wait
approximately one hundred square
a complex wearing jackets and one last
thing the suspect is armed when considered
extremely dangerous in company
with suspect number one in.
Fact. I think proximity five weight
approximately one hundred pounds dark
complected wearing
a dress went to mass Thank you. For
that radio call again two minutes or.
Looks like we have to run for.
It but. I got an idea it may not
work at least to Chad it's obvious he
doesn't know much about them as you. Do if
you do but I got to Alaska
to get started Lisa Bloom or
a similar one here and I get to pursue.
Especially this is what I do like to do
you shift into drive pushed
out of the break up.
I guess I think I went out on top people
in the gas pedal to the floorboard I tried
to lure him in for.
Just
a chance. When I hit him. But we can
we start making the few seconds I
need. Let's just pretend
a kid got us. From Fort.
Chatham just after take.
Me.
Seriously.
I think the car when you started it.
If you say. THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU for
the
THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
the shit
head
. THANK YOU
THANK YOU
THE
Thank you. Thank you didn't
have.
You so thanks for the visit
had the thank you didn't
have
it have.
Thank you
the thank you.
The day. The day that we
THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU for
the THANK YOU THANK YOU red hot the
director in writing thank
you thank you for. Red.
White.
And.
The just the way from the Carolinas to.
My head so I don't want to die.
I don't. Think this is
a. Four
minute.
It's
a car and started talking to the public
pressure. Get in the car and started. Just
a minute if you want the car to run I want
to live those extra few minutes now I
have to check the bumper
pressure. All right. But it did
a really good.
Started out.
You will get much really can't. To me.
I was just feeling you but.
Right now.
I thank you you are
a big. One Today bloomer. The
.
Get up. I said get out.
Move.
If you were sick or stupid. Trying to.
To do something I did nothing. But
a pretty good address that it's
a go you mother did something
like this up as been
a wrecked car who knows how sometimes they
get parted all the pressure to take it
out and clean it to eat it too but it's
not working pressure needs to be cleaned.
And it won't take very long. To
get nothing out you think you're
fooling me don't you. Take interest in
the cards don't you that then why did
I break the cock and realize I was
destined. For you gotta do is pregnant
now seen that done so you print. Gods
a gas bubble there. Doris
get McCartney started when I tell you nobody
gets no car but me. I'm going to prime
it somebody at the Gap that'll just never
you mind but I guess not covering.
At least.
Louis.
Louis. You.
Were really.
Cool.
You. Lose. Your cool looking.
The only thing I.
I.
Thank. You.
By now ya. I'll find you. Find your. Way
out but I.
Think. Being. A good.
Day I. Am.
It's.
Thank.
You and.
It
was
.
Live.
Live
a little. Live
.
The.
Lead
.
And.
Illegible.
League.
Please.
Thank
. You
are.
I. Wouldn't. Have.
Gotten.
It.
Says six pts.
It's. Because.
I get.
To. Live.
Up.
To. It.
I. I.
Line up once more follow out
a curve ball just missed the all tonight
going to very little. BALL That's right on
. The Incidentally there was
a good scene here for you then join the
dyed in the Red Lake I want to come on now
and you'll enjoy it here at Dodger Stadium
a gorgeous day here in ground everybody
wonderful and I were set on the bases
loaded bottom of the first then run verily
out there thirty the green interior of
the red one that'll. Be as if I
were to light up the Verily That's
all I want to
thank
you thank heaven.
For war. Today.